Doll & Richards Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Financial Records, 1871-1973, bulk 1902-1969, Series 5:; (Boxes 18-69, 79, BV81-112; 55 linear feet)
  - Sales Records, circa 1883, 1901-1973, bulk 1902-1968, 5.2:
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 54)
      - Nos. C31,300-C31,399, December 14, 1929 - January 24, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C31,400-C31,499, January 23 - March 5, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C31,500-C31,599, March 5 - April 11, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C31,600-C31,699, April 11 - May 1, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C31,700-C31,799, May 1 - June 2, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Nos. C31,800-C31,899, June 2 - July 14, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 55)
      - Nos. C31,900-C31,999, July 15 - October 2, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C32,000-C32,099, October 2 - November 13, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C32,100-C32,199, November 13 - December 2, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C32,200-C32,299, December 2-22, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C32,300-C32,399, December 22, 1930 - January 19, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C32,400-C32,499, January 21 - March 26, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C32,500-C32,599, March 30 - May 22, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C32,600-C32,699, May 22 - July 30, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C32,700-C32,799, July 30 - October 28, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C32,800-C32,899, October 28 - December 21, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C32,900-C32,999, December 21, 1931 - February 27, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C33,000-C33,099, February 29 - April 6, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C33,100-C33,199, April 7 - June 6, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C33,200-C33,299, May 12 - August 15, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C33,300-C33,399, August 15 - October 14, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C33,400-C33,499, October 18 - November 26, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C33,500-C33,599, November 26, 1932 - January 1, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C33,600-C33,699, January 3 - February 7, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C33,700-C33,799, February 7 - April 12, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C33,800-C33,899, April 12 - June 6, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C33,900-C33,999, June 7 - July 18, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C34,000-C34,099, July 18 - October 2, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C34,100-C34,199, October 2 - November 4, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C34,200-C34,299, November 4 - December 5, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C34,300-C34,399, December 5, 1933 - January 8, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C34,400-C34,499, January 6 - February 9, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - Nos. C34,500-C34,599, February 9 - March 23, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 56)
      - Nos. C34,600-C34,699, March 23 - June 4, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C34,700-C34,799, June 4 - August 17, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C34,800-C34,899, August 17 - October 18, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C34,900-C34,999, October 18 - November 20, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C35,000-C35,099, November 20, 1934 - January 2, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C36,000-C36,099, January 2 - February 25, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C37,000-C37,099, February 25 - April 5, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C38,000-C38,099, April 8 - June 12, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C38,100-C38,199, June 12 - September 20, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C38,200-C38,299, September 20 - November 1, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C38,300-C38,399, November 1 - December 3, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C38,400-C38,499, December 4, 1935 - January 13, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C38,500-C38,599, January 13 - February 20, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C38,600-C38,699, February 20 - April 13, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C38,700-C38,799, April 13 - June 3, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C38,800-C38,899, June 3 - August 5, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C38,900-C38,999, August 6 - October 22, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C39,000-C39,099, October 7 - November 30, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C39,100-C39,199, December 1, 1936 - January 27, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C39,200-C39,299, January 28 - March 6, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C39,300-C39,399, March 8 - May 7, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C39,400-C39,499, May 7 - July 15, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C39,500-C39,599, July 17 - September 13, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C39,600-C39,699, September 14 - November 3, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C39,700-C39,799, November 4 - December 9, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C39,800-C39,899, December 9, 1937 - January 29, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 57)
      - Nos. C39,900-C39,999, January 31 - March 29, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C40,000-C40,099, March 30 - June 14, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C40,100-C40,199, June 14 - August 31, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C40,200-C40,299, August 31 - October 20, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C40,300-C40,399, October 20 - November 18, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C40,400-C40,499, November 19 - December 27, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C40,500-C40,599, December 27, 1938 - January 31, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C40,600-C40,699, January 31 - March 9, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C40,700-C40,799, March 9 - May 1, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C40,800-C40,899, May 3 - June 30, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C40,900-C40,999, June 30 - September 15, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C41,000-C41,099, September 16 - November 2, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C41,100-C41,199, November 2 - December 13, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C41,200-C41,299, December 13, 1939 - January 19, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C41,300-C41,399, January 20 - March 2, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C41,400-C41,499, January 29, 1940; March 4-8, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C41,500-C41,599, February 17 - October 4, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C41,600-C41,699, March 26 - April 30, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C41,700-C41,799, April 30 - June 12, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C41,800-C41,899, June 14 - September 19, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C41,900-C41,999, September 19 - October 29, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C42,000-C42,099, October 29 - December 12, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C42,100-C42,199, December 12, 1940 - January 21, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C42,200-C42,299, January 21 - February 27, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C42,300-C42,399, February 28 - April 8, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C42,400-C42,499, April 8 - May 8, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 58)
      - Nos. C42,500-C42,599, May 10 - June 18, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C42,600-C42,699, June 18 - September 23, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C42,700-C42,799, September 25 - November 15, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C42,800-C42,899, November 17 - December 26, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C42,900-C42,999, December 26, 1941 - February 2, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C43,000-C43,099, February 2 - September 22, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C43,100-C43,199, September 25 - October 29, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C43,200-C43,299, October 29 - December 7, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C43,300-C43,399, December 9, 1942 - February 19, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C43,400-C43,499, February 19 - April 12, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C43,500-C43,599, April 13 - May 27, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C43,600-C43,699, May 27 - July 12, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C43,700-C43,799, July 12 - September 10, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C43,800-C43,899, September 10 - November 3, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C43,900-C43,999, November 4 - December 20, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C44,000-C44,099, December 20, 1943 - February 15, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C44,100-C44,199, February 16 - April 6, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C44,200-C44,299, April 6 - May 9, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C44,300-C44,399, May 10 - June 14, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C44,400-C44,499, June 14 - July 28, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C44,500-C44,599, July 28 - September 18, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C44,600-C44,699, September 19 - October 24, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C44,700-C44,799, October 24 - November 29, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 59)
      - Nos. C44,800-C44,899, December 5, 1944 - January 11, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C44,900-C44,999, January 11 - February 27, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C45,000-C45,099, February 27 - April 12, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C45,100-C45,199, April 12 - May 28, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C45,200-C45,299, May 28 - June 30, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C45,300-C45,399, June 30 - August 30, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C45,400-C45,499, August 30 - October 3, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C45,500-C45,599, October 3 - November 12, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C45,600-C45,699, November 13 - December 20, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C45,700-C45,799, December 24, 1945 - January 24, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C45,800-C45,899, January 24 - March 14, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C45,900-C45,999, March 14 - April 18, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C46,000-C46,099, April 18 - May 23, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C46,100-C46,199, May 24 - July 2, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C46,200-C46,299, July 2 - September 16, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C46,300-C46,399, September 16 - October 30, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C46,400-C46,499, October 31 - December 9, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C46,500-C46,599, December 9, 1946 - February 14, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C46,600-C46,699, January 16 - April 30, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C46,700-C46,799, January 24 - March 31, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C46,800-C46,899, March 31 - May 17, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C46,900-C46,999, May 17 - July 24, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C47,000-C47,099, July 26 - September 22, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 60)
      - Nos. C47,100-C47,199, September 22 - November 12, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C47,200-C47,299, November 12, 1947 - January 13, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C47,300-C47,399, January 13 - March 18, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C47,400-C47,499, March 18 - April 13, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C47,500-C47,599, April 13 - June 7, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C47,600-C47,699, June 7 - August 16, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C47,700-C47,799, August 16 - October 6, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C47,800-C47,899, October 6 - November 20, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C47,900-C47,999, November 20, 1948 - January 10, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C48,000-C48,099, January 10 - February 25, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C48,100-C48,199, February 28 - April 18, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C48,200-C48,299, April 18 - June 11, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C48,300-C48,399, June 11 - September 12, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C48,400-C48,499, September 12 - October 18, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C48,500-C48,599, October 19 - December 2, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C48,600-C48,699, December 2, 1949 - January 25, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C48,700-C48,799, January 26 - April 17, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C48,800-C48,899, April 18 - June 19, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C48,900-C48,999, June 19 - September 15, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C49,000-C49,099, September 15 - November 9, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C49,100-C49,199, November 11 - December 27, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C49,200-C49,299, December 27, 1950 - March 12, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 61)
      - Nos. C49,300-C49,399, March 12 - May 1, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C49,400-C49,499, May 2 - June 19, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C49,500-C49,599, June 19 - September 4, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C49,600-C49,699, September 4 - October 24, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C49,700-C49,790, October 26 - November 30, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C49,806-C49,899, December 1, 1951 - January 16, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C49,900-C49,999, January 16 - March 11, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C50,000-C50,099, March 11 - May 7, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C50,100-C50,199, May 8 - August 4, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C50,200-C50,299, August 5 - October 20, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C50,300-C50,399, August 22 - November 1, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C50,400-C50,499, September 9 - December 1, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C50,500-C50,599, December 1, 1952 - January 20, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C50,600-C50,699, January 21 - March 23, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C50,700-C50,799, March 24 - May 22, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C50,800-C50,899, May 22 - July 27, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C50,900-C50,999, July 27 - October 9, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C51,000-C51,099, October 9 - December 1, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C51,100-C51,199, December 1, 1953 - February 12, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C51,200-C51,298, February 15 - April 21, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C51,300-C51,399, April 21 - June 5, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C51,400-C51,499, June 7 - September 8, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 62)
      - Nos. C51,500-C51,599, September 8 - October 29, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C51,600-C51,699, October 28, 1954 - January 7, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C51,700-C51,799, January 8 - March 10, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C51,800-C51,899, March 10 - May 14, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C51,900-C51,999, May 17 - July 11, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C52,000-C52,099, July 11 - October 6, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C52,100-C52,199, October 7 - November 29, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C52,200-C52,299, November 29, 1955 - January 27, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C52,300-C52,399, January 27 - April 24, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C52,400-C52,499, April 26 - June 16, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C52,500-C52,599, June 18 - October 3, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C52,600-C52,699, October 1 - November 21, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C52,700-C52,799, November 20, 1956 - February 18, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C52,800-C52,899, February 18 - May 13, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C52,900-C52,999, May 14 - July 25, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C53,000-C53,099, July 25 - October 15, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C53,100-C53,199, October 15 - December 3, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C53,200-C53,299, December 3, 1957 - February 15, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C53,300-C53,399, February 15 - May 6, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C53,400-C53,499, May 9 - July 15, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 63)
      - Nos. C53,500-C53,599, July 24 - October 2, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C53,600-C53,699, October 3 - November 19, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C53,700-C53,799, November 20, 1958 - February 26, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C53,800-C53,899, February 26 - April 3, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C53,900-C53,999, April 3 - July 30, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C54,000-C54,099, August 4 - October 28, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C54,100-C54,199, October 28, 1959 - January 4, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C54,200-C54,299, January 4 - May 2, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C54,300-C54,399, May 2 - August 11, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C54,400-C54,499, August 11 - November 18, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C54,500-C54,599, November 23, 1960 - April 8, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C54,600-C54,699, April 8 - June 26, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C54,700-C54,799, June 27 - October 31, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C54,800-C54,899, November 1, 1961 - March 23, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C54,900-C54,999, March 23 - August 21, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C55,000-C55,099, August 21, 1962 - January 10, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C55,100-C55,199, January 10 - August 6, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C55,200-C55,299, August 6, 1963 - January 21, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Nos. D0101-D0199, September 23 - December 7, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Nos. D0200-D0299, December 9, 1925 - January 21, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Nos. D0300-D0399, January 21 - April 21, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 64)
      - Nos. D0400-D0499, April 23 - September 3, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Nos. D0500-D0599, September 7 - October 28, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Nos. D0600-D0699, October 28 - November 29, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Nos. D0700-D0799, November 29 - December 23, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Nos. D0800-D0899, December 24, 1926 - January 31, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Nos. D0900-D0999, January 31 - March 19, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Nos. D1,000-D1,099, March 24 - May 10, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Nos. D1,100-D1,199, May 10 - July 12, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Nos. D1,200-D1,299, July 12 - October 14, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Nos. D1,300-D1,399, October 17 - November 14, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Nos. D1,400-D1,499, November 14 - December 15, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Nos. D1,500-D1,599, December 15, 1927 - January 13, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Nos. D1,600-D1,699, January 14 - February 28, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Nos. D1,700-D1,799, February 28 - April 10, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Nos. D1,800-D1,899, April 11 - May 11, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Nos. D1,900-D1,999, May 12 - June 28, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Nos. D2,000-D2,099, June 29 - October 15, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Nos. D2,100-D2,199, October 15 - December 18, 1928 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Nos. D2,200-D2,299, December 18, 1928 - April 22, 1929 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Nos. D2,300-D2,399, April 22 - August 16, 1929 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Nos. D2,400-D2,499, August 16 - November 22, 1929 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Nos. D2,500-D2,599, November 22, 1929 - February 17, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Nos. D2,600-D2,699, February 17 - May 28, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Nos. D2,700-D2,799, May 31 - October 1, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Nos. D2,800-D2,899, October 1 - December 3, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Nos. D2,900-D2,999, December 4, 1930 - March 23, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Nos. D3,000-D3,099, March 25 - September 14, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Nos. D3,100-D3,199, September 15 - November 19, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 65)
      - Nos. D3,200-D3,299, November 21, 1931 - March 14, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Nos. D3,300-D3,399, March 15 - September 14, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Nos. D3,400-D3,499, September 21, 1932 - February 6, 1933 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Nos. D3,500-D3,599, February 6 - July 20, [1934] (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Nos. D3,600-D3,699, August 6 - November 28, 1934 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Nos. D3,700-D3,799, December 3, 1934 - April 5, 1935 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Nos. D3,800-D3,899, April 8 - October 1, 1935 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Nos. D3,900-D3,999, October 1 - December 16, 1935 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Nos. D4,000-D4,099, December 16, 1935 - May 20, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Nos. D4,100-D4,199, May 20 - October 8, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Nos. D4,200-D4,299, October 9 - November 30, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Nos. D4,300-D4,399, December 1, 1936 - March 5, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Nos. D4,400-D4,499, March 8 - July 2, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Nos. D4,500-D4,599, July 2 - November 10, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Nos. D4,600-D4,699, November 10, 1937 - January 15, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Nos. D4,700-D4,799, January 15 - June 7, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Nos. D4,800-D4,899, June 7 - November 15, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Nos. D4,900-D4,999, November 15, 1938 - March 3, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Nos. D5,000-D5,099, March 3 - September 27, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Nos. D5,100-D5,199, September 27 - December 4, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Nos. D5,200-D5,299, December 5, 1939 - March 28, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Nos. D5,300-D5,399, March 28 - June 4, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - Nos. D5,400-D5,499, June 5 - October 16, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Nos. D5,500-D5,599, October 16, 1940 - January 14, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Nos. D5,600-D5,699, January 15 - May 29, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - Nos. D5,700-D5,799, May 31 - October 9, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 26)
      - Nos. D5,800-D5,899, October 14 - December 16, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 66)
      - Nos. D5,900-D5,999, December 17, 1941 - May 26, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Nos. D6,000-D6,099, May 26 - June 3, 1942; May 6 - December 29, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Nos. D6,100-D6,199, December 29, 1943 - September 29, 1944 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Nos. D6,200-D6,299, October 10, 1944 - March 30, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Nos. D6,300-D6,399, March 30 - June 26, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Nos. D6,400-D6,499, June 26 - November 8, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Nos. D6,500-D6,598, November 8, 1945 - April 29, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Nos. D6,600-D6,699, April 30 - August 7, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Nos. D6,700-D6,799, August 12 - November 8, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Nos. D6,800-D6,899, November 11 - December 20, 1946; April 30 - July 22, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Nos. D6,900-D6,999, July 29 - November 26, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Nos. D7,000-D7,099, November 28, 1947 - April 8, 1948 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Nos. D7,100-D7,199, February 24 - June 30, 1948 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Nos. D7,200-D7,299, June 30 - November 17, 1948 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Nos. D7,300-D7,399, November 3, 1948 - March 30, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Nos. D7,400-D7,499, March 31 - September 28, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Nos. D7,500-D7,599, September 28, 1949 - January 25, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Nos. D7,600-D7,699, January 27 - July 10, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Nos. D7,700-D7,799, July 10 - November 29, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Nos. D7,800-D7,899, November 29, 1950 - May 12, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Nos. D7,900-D7,981, May 18 - November 24, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Nos. D8,009-D8,099, November 24, 1951 - April 21, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Nos. D8,100-D8,199, April 21 - October 11, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Nos. D8,200-D8,299, October 20, 1952 - May 7, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 67)